By the way, tomorrow we're going to give you
another reading called
the innings review,
the settings review. It's an image
that should remind you of an idea. I've done
about 100, almost 200. I've prepared
about 200, very heavy double-header, the last
three years, and I haven't finished.
But
then we were supposed to discover it
in Thailand, and I got so busy, which is
very unusual, that it takes me so long to
cover 78 shows. So
tomorrow you're going to have another reading,
and they're just images, colors, and you can
test yourselves to see if you
remember what they mean. I'll explain it
in these 8 years
[Music].
And if you become a teacher, you
can choose to specialize, like if you
go to law school, you can choose to
be a criminal lawyer or a
business lawyer. Intellectual. So you have an
option where there are teachers. He's the
most... the training says there's a basic
course, and if there's one,
you can specialize, like specializing
in meditation.
Some people, instead of teaching the
courses, would like to teach the
meditations,
or maybe they might invite you to a
company.
They want you to teach them meditation,
and they don't care.  The courses, so
everyone should have the courses, that's
the foundation, that's the basis of
law school. You can add a
specialty so you can be an
expert in the mind, and for us, it will be
the Green meditations. We'll be going through those,
so tomorrow we'll start
reviewing about 200 meditations from
the last 8 years, and you don't have to
learn them, but if you want, you can be
a special lawyer specializing in
just handling car accidents or something like that.
So, some help will suffice. There will
also be a specialty
called "
the one who organizes retreats," the
waste organizer. Some people are
interested, and some, I don't know, if you're
the type of person who wants to help
people through retreats from a few
weeks to three years, then you can
specialize
in long retreats. And we're also
thinking that there could be a
specialty in topics like cameras, and we
see it that way. We've done it for five years, and
it's the best comment from the greatest, the
greatest, the greatest of the
diamonds, and it has many, and if you can
learn them, you can have exits, and
so, this title is, and there you can
have a specialty in cameras, and
some are interested in the
Diamond workshop and you can have a
Messi specialty too, good in
those things
[Music]
we're going to design a course, activate,
specialize in aggression, to be, I started, I started
in October of
last year, it was going to take years to finish, so
if you want to specialize in
agriculture, try to come every October,
we're reviewing the comment
of the book "Wisdom of Refusing
Once," it's the most famous and it's the most and it's very, very, very
incredible, very good,
so you don't have to do any of
those specializations, you can
just have a degree and you can teach if there is,
if it's certified, but if you want to
specialize, what you can add is a
tweet, master, a specialization,
meditations, retreats in rhymes, which is like,
maximum, the room or a slaughterhouse, so they're going to get ready, there's this,
this post, historical, of the next
crime,
to Lobo,
once it falls,
very well, we're going to start with hunger
as new material,
if we're going to see,
space, and in Monterrey 3,
both,
La Pampa, well,
space, pie,
this unique tree, educate ones in this
aspect,
well,
space, pie
in the restaurant, for my level, it's already
here, there's
the first of  The
six negative emotions, and the main one is
desire. It's
like another school. Now that you
have a complete view of what
the training in Asia will be like, and of the four
plus the five schools, you can
appreciate how long it lasts. They teach different
levels,
so one teaching has many
different levels.
Many people will see different things in the
teachings. With the same words, I'll say the ups and
downs of how to think: don't want
anything, don't buy new things,
don't wear nice clothes, live in a
cave, and that's okay. There's a place for
that, especially if you're distracted by
material things, if you're of that
age, and you're trying to make money
and suddenly you die
and lose everything. So that's okay, this
kind of teaching. But at a
higher level, what we really want to do
is learn to share. So
desire becomes the opposite of
sharing. It's okay to want a
chocolate chip cookie,
but if you like it, you do
n't have to share. That's all.
Imagine an emotion, the emotion. There's no
desire. Smart,
share your cookies because you want more
cookies, and it's not an emotion. It's something bad
about it. You know you'll never be able to eat
anything in your entire life.
no paper tape unless you
share it with someone, it's not bad,
a kid, that's the intelligent desire
[Music]
because it makes
if we take it as if the desire were an
attachment to his body
in the traditions there are traditions and
traditional meditations that we're going to
talk about, we're going to talk about a
slavery for combat and it's called
meduca bomba or whatever group
can say that it's the one that governs
and it sounds like kangaroo that in in
vitro tennis to combat half for
compartment who is and it means
from upa mit burford this your peace
means it's beautiful, it sucks, it's an
agreement, it's a measure in the ugly to
reality
efe jmr psh keyboard gives a very
famous example skin routing scene
and here they don't teach it
but you can do it here if you want it
's an old meditation of inhabiting ma
in which there is something left,
a disease with this disease what you
lose your legs
like gangrene here
and it starts to spread
you can see the skull bone and
then you start, person meditates, if you
're seeing your whole skull is kobe,
then all your skulls that don't have
skin and don't imitate that descent  Your body
until your whole body is as it is
and then everything falls apart
and the building starts to get
old. The floor,
originally we made all the
buildings with the cloud of earth. This
building is ours and our dream was that it would
blend back into the
earth. If one day the
adobe monument melts back into the
earth, let it blend in.
We just blended a house with it and that's
how buildings age.
Then you go to the highway and all the
cars break down on the road.
Then you go to Tucson too. Someday it's going to
be empty. We don't know when, but
someday it will be. There
probably won't be enough
water in Tucson and they're going to leave.
So this meditation, I mean, it doesn't
reach
California and New York. So you empty, you dry up
the ocean, all of this.
This is called the
skeleton meditation and it does nothing the same and has another
climate.
How can you fix your desire for
things, for people?
You can do a meditation called "me
to," which means
something more than Rosa
Jennings to Klatten. It means for
activities with you.
What does it mean? It's the
Red Sea.
If you can't see, stop seeing
someone's wife and if you think you're going to
start doing bad things with  They just
peel them off
and it looks like a steak. We're steaks.
Disgusting meditation. So the
next time I see this person who's already
married, it's a lower school. It's
a lower school, and Mind Network
might not work in the end. And if not, that's
the definition of a lower school: it might not work. It might work,
but it might not work.
A better meditation to make from the
higher schools,
because if you steal this person from their
husband,
then the karma is that you're always going to be
losing their partners. I don't want that. I want them to stay.
If it's a
better method than to fight over the
skin,
but sometimes this works. It's like
aspirin. So many times this medium tension
of trying to peel them off, flaying
them, that called the red lens.
So the second name,
Hilarion's disturbance, after this person, sooner or
later, Samurai says something similar, and their
arm will disconnect from their body.
Running
a punishment without before, in which they
connected your parts, used your arms
and legs on horses, and then they
threw the horses and tore your
body apart and hung your body parts
in four different cities to
demonstrate the punishment.  And they would leave them there
for years. This leg from this profile is
very disgusting.
To dismember the person, you strike the
parts as a sign to others. The
other people, we are
all going to dismember this
woman you want to steal from her husband,
or this husband who wants to steal his
wife from his beard, also dismember them.
In the end, they are just flesh.
That will help you not to have desires, but
everything works. Some laws, the
seeds, they always work, they always
work. These are the lowest school.
We have that word for it. I know
that word, but I looked it up, and it means
that they will also be able to go well. Their
skin
[Music]. Their
left lips, their
beautiful ears, they will be able to go into a box
somewhere. And two, you visualize this.
18 says if you fall in love with a woman,
first check her sleeve.
This is how it will look
[Music].
And it means that your skin,
then if you have an attachment to another
partner, someone else, then think about
how they begin to
conceive. In a way, it is one of
the five aggregates, and bones after it
rots. I think of my mom sometimes, of
everything.  What's left of her are
bones in a box. If I could
dig up her boxes, they're just bones, and they'd
look like someone else's bones. You don't
know. I wouldn't know. If my mom said, "And what does
this woman want? What does she want?" She's
tough. They're just bones in the end. They're just bones,
and we're all just samples. So it's not
that sexy.
As long as it's Halloween,
there's a maximum, a
more formal teaching
in this meditation. You want to go
deeper? I knew you'd say yes, so it
was, and I got it for
you. There's the plasma for migrations,
the scriptures, the plasma for the middle
course of the course of gay, which means
the school, the middle path, the lowest, and
a very good presentation in which they give
nine steps for this meditation on
adultery. There are nine steps, and they only
mention some of them.
So when they teach the new ones, the
nine parts of the disgusting meditation, they
list which ones have been measured
for each one. So there are nine parts of
the meditation, and there are nine parts
to fix it. I'm going
to teach you the deepest one. That's why
this tear is so slow. It's
going to take like 20. We're about halfway through.
Here's number 1.
If...  You are attracted to this
person's body. Look at their
breasts, look at their hips, look at their
muscles, and the specific medication.
Velasco, think about how their
skin rots, their arms, their head. If you have a
problem with the breasts or biceps of
someone else's wife,
if you want to meditate on how they
rot, how breasts or
arms rot, very well, they are happy.
It is the man of meditation, and see
if you have a sexual attraction towards
another person, or I want to have sex with
this person who is already married.
If by then, basic back,
imagine those who are penetrating
that beautiful thing in which you want to,
even the larvae, how we like the
small ones or small flies, and they eat and
comment on things that you take into account. These
that you download in the earth, you find a
misano, but sometimes you find a
long one, and they are also going to eat you
because the new ones are everywhere.
You have fly eggs,
and they are going to eat you as you are today. They
will be. You already
have the penetrators in your skin, and you are
going to make me their food and money. You are going to
make me their dinner. Today it could be  Your senator, we
already know,
number 3.
If you're attracted to the scent of
this person's pheromones,
if you get close to them and they see you,
I'm attracted to you. They say that
menstruation has pheromones, so
if a woman is menstruating,
men are like animals and there's a
subconscious attraction to the smell of another
human being. And if you have this problem, he
says, imagine
the smell of her rotten water and pus
coming out of her body.
About earthquakes or tornadoes or
mass murders, sometimes they say that the
smell of a decaying body is the
worst smell in the world. I don't know, but I
think he reads it at a funeral once,
but it must be him. It's supposed to be the
closest smell.
Once I had a meeting with one of the
richest people in the world
who was going to support one of our
projects, and then we were supposed to
go to New York, and
one of our congregants died, one of
our monks,
and I was very scared because here
was this person who could support, he
says, there for 1000 years,
but I have to go to the funeral to
Taking care of this person,
so I canceled and went to the funeral,
and he was there
on the metal table, and the place was
very cold because they don't want the smell,
and there he was, naked on this metal table,
and then the law draws his
blood and replaces it with
alcohol, so they were taking
his blood, that's how it keeps you for 3
or 4 days, otherwise, so that your family
can come see you, they have to take your
blood before it hardens.
I had to do these
bardic prayers, and I sat there for like two or three
hours and said the bardic prayers, but it
was very difficult.
So, if you are attracted to
a person's grief or their perfume or
aftershave, think about how they will
smell two days after they die.
The new Ford number four,
and the person you are attracted to is very
good at wearing jewelry like earrings,
necklaces, bracelets, you ca
n't be who. Then the
peel
is when we do the steak meditation,
specifically in the ancient
texts, if you are attracted to their way of
dressing, their fashion, or they dress very
well, or in  Vigor, Ticos, very beautiful things,
then skinning Gasteiz, well, this
ornament
is disgusting.
Some women are like that, and the
beautiful McKinley, the Mexican women
have a very beautiful golden color on their
bodies.
If you are attracted to the color of a
person, to the color of their skin,
Greenstein, then that's the green thing.
America, the
fungus discriminates against
America,
and the body, when it rots, turns
green, and green things grow like mushrooms. It comes out
as a thermal,
tena, like green, it
means that your skin turns green.
So if you are attracted to its color, I
changed the green,
the old Havana, with an old banana,
CP.
So if you are attracted to its
Amazon, to its muscles, to the year, since for
me it means
guard, to manage, it means their
bodies, to their muscles, saw towards their
food.
In India, in
India, if you are fat, it is beautiful. It is
like in Europe 500 years ago, it means
you have money, that you are not hungry, and
then anyone who was big
was considered more attractive. Now in
America it is the opposite, you have to be
too skinny
and unhealthy. It keeps
changing;
skinny is popular, sometimes fat is
popular.
So any shape in those days,
big was true.
If these  Two big ones just think about Link
and how they're going to get eaten
by insects and mice, and after they
die, their bodies are going to be
eaten by cockroaches,
tick-tock tick-tock, and stuff like that. And that's
number 6, and it's Castell. They're already disgusted,
and it takes a lot of imagination to be
attracted to something. It's a lot of deceiving
yourself to notice that they're dead meat.
If you study for a long time, it's hard to
be sexually attracted to someone. You do
n't see them if you think green. That's why
people from the wine network behave,
forget who
's really there.
[Music]
By the way, in a higher school, you can
never be attracted. High
school, in the highest school, that's the
goal. It ca
n't be beautiful forever, and you don't
have to see it that way. It can be
forever. Plant the seed in a
super safe body forever, and that's
why we feel, because we feel the
possibility of that. That's why we're
attracted to
others, because we feel the possibility
that they're angels. That's what we
are, what gets into me, and other
people, because in a way  Mainly, you're still going to
have everything, and you're going to have two
arms, two legs, it's still going to be
on one head.
So the school, more help, Lenin
should feel that the CNE 'doesn't make a
body,' and Malaga paints it badly. I
like to call it a
living diamond, super sexy, super attractive.
Houston verdict:
if you're attracted to the way the
person walks down the street,
then guys walk like that too. There's
the beauty of movement.
So you do the meditation where you
put your head over there, your leg over there,
because that's how it's going to be. Use your arms
according to the diversity of your feet. Your
head is going to be divorced from the things
that are attracted to the movement, by
how they move them, because those arms are going to be taken out
of your body. And
there are parts of the
body that are bones, and the most
attractive are the teeth. Or she has
such beautiful white teeth,
and the other shapes of the bones, like
a ballet dancer.
And in some countries,
when they choose children for
acting or ballet, they
measure their bones to see if they have the
right proportions.  What
Andreas talked about yesterday, you can measure all the
bones
and predict if the person is going to be more
attractive or stronger. Even from my
thirteen children, so, and setting goals,
faction, you have attraction to the part
of the bones of your body. So what I
think is that the skull is the most powerful in
meditation,
and its beautiful,
sexy teeth are going to be rotting on the ground.
The last high face, and Lazzarini explains
in Bonn, let's see if Petit in India, and that
in ancient times it wasn't a
tradition to burn bodies and burn
deer. FP, gum, and social, is
particularly attractive.
I'm going to try to attract the collection, already
the shape of this person.
I try to get ahead and see them burning
in their cremation, to see their body, what
hands, lieutenants,
this skin, to know the color,
these chips, this beautiful shape. Just
imagine it's burning during their funeral.
Very well,
when I was on a flight, I was in
India,
so his skull fell off the stove
towards us,
everyone was scared. Here's our lama from
last week, and his skull is
rolling towards us, and
everyone was scared. We're going to be burning, we're already...
They are depressed, and
the meditations are very good, they can do without problems,
especially with the attraction to
someone else's partner,
even your own partner attracted to
them, attached to them in an unhealthy way.
In the lowest school, my definition of
the lowest school is that sometimes it works,
sometimes it doesn't.
That's the lowest school for me. The
highest school always works. The
school of
seeds for
diamond bodies and not doing these stupid
meditations is more efficient.
Okay,
but by the way, this is something that
people don't talk about in media trainings,
in a Design Edition teacher training.
This job is to learn the lower schools
too. It's your job to learn
these lower schools too, and
because, for the same reason that Buddha
solved it in the first place, which is that
someone can respond to this
treatment. There are different vitamins.
Some vitamins...
I have a friend, my sister, got
sick because they gave her vitamin D
that they were going to remove her kidney, and she was a victim
because it was too much vitamin D.
So,
different vitamins work for different
bodies. We all have different bodies, different
minds.
If you learn all the schools...
Because you're going to find someone, whoever
is your student, who needs this
meditation,
or teacher. I'm so attracted to another,
this beautiful woman who is married. I don't know
what to do.
Let me teach you the Velasco meditation
because it has nine parts and it's every
day. This is where you learn everything,
learn all the schools because you might
need it. You might find
someone who needs it. Okay, it's very good to
have a tool, a
very big toolbox. I have a
friend who is a plumber, and he's
66. So we have, well, Spin,
and he's been adding tools to his
cart for 50 years. That's a good
tool. You
should be with this
66-year-old plumber and have all the tools
of a Buddha, all the help that
this meditation gives us, for five or ten
years. You go out and say, "I
have the branch that's for you. I have the
thing that you need to learn."
The Lord is useful to someone.
Very well, we are in the second
main negative emotion, and by the way, to
remind you that there are six
main negative emotions. Sit and Mary, we are going
to do meditations on them because if they
are primary, you should have them every
day. Two built  In those 84,000 plus
the actions of Buddhism, teeth opening, he
also said doubt, I can't remember
the obvious ones, he said
the top 10 of those days, the
main bad actions: 3 of the body,
4 of speech, and 3 of the mind. The reason they
are the top ten is because you do them
all day, every day, once,
not twice, every half hour. We are
all human. On this team, six
main ones of the 84,000 emotions, in
the top 6, you must be doing them every
day.
We must be doing this
plan, and then, as I mentioned, 20
secondary emotions and
negative secondary emotions. He mentioned them as if he were going to
teach them.
So, I have an idea to ask
Lama Stanley to teach his book
tomorrow. They are there, you have enough
time to prepare it,
and then you will be taught the ones
of life. He translated them into more of my
suggestions. Stanley, it's my house, think about it for
a couple of hours, and I have already had
this year, this year, and then
talk about it, we are going to embarrass you in
front of everyone.
Maybe it will be painted, but some of
them here by
then, but I mean  I don't just
read the list, it talks about this is
my experience with this. We do
n't really know if other people
are having this experience, but
we know that we are, and that's why I
'm not doing it. And Tula,
then maybe we won't
finish all six before tomorrow, but
you're going to put the 20 there in the middle.
So, number two of the
main ones are
anger
in general,
but also towards the weather, towards
traffic, towards your finances, towards your
shoes.
You can have anger towards anything.
We are very flexible about our
anger,
and you can let your anger go.
Angry people are
like fury, the mind gets hurt. In that
word,
hard, rough, but very good to play. It's
Grey Chela's nickname at the monastery.
All the monks have a nickname, and they're calling me "the little cheese,"
which is my skin. It's not very, very
soft.
That was my monastery
nickname, the most famous one at the monastery.
Again, we
went, and they were having a
debate contest, a
competition, and we went because we
were paying for the amounts. We didn't have
any money. Everyone was
eating rice. We made everyone a
fried one, which is
delicious. It's
supposed to  I had to debate to
show us game full that it was because
we're paying for everyone,
so there's a place in the debate where you
quote if you're in a book and it says it's
the sutra, it says it knows it has this
type, so we make ships,
guys,
what does it mean, like fried
for 20 years,
please don't call me up here, so
the word here, that experience,
a main means that your mind is like
the bark of a tree, it's not very fast and
very good to touch, it's not smooth, the
word in Sanskrit is maniema, new man,
you, the one
who speaks gently, is my new sui, it
means action, smooth like velvet,
like silk, it's
very smooth, it has the 'number two',
you want to hurt someone, you want to
do something to them,
my specialty is passive aggression, it's
a special aggression, a special type
of aggression,
going out to nations and they don't tell you there isn't any
and you tell them, deal, that's okay, that's
nice, week, I won't need it for
a week, I'm not going to eat for a week, it's
okay, I can do hashish, I'll
just be hungry for a week, I'll
pay the money myself, but don't
worry,
you have the right to say no
and  I'm probably going to have to
stay in bed suffering. This is a
way of attacking someone in a sweet way.
This is called passive aggression.
That's my specialty. Everything has its
own specialty. It took me a long time
to realize.
So there are different ways to
hurt people, to attack people, and
sometimes later with our mouths.
This maternal line,
also following the
garden, which is like Salvador Marín, this
rough mind, and it's...
and look
[Music]
something that triggers a negative emotion,
what makes you go so that what
makes you fast, and what itches you... three
buttons to press. You have
six buttons in every human being, and we're going to
study them, and it's part of 3 ni
teams. It's all the next inning, Sex
Way. 6 ways to press
a person's buttons. One is Miguel, I guide myself
from the scientific park to this person's life.
When you see a person, there's a person you do
n't like, and if you're not around
them, everything is fine. If suddenly they
disappear, a party is
invited by this idiot,
then you see them and it ruins your whole
night. You don't have fun at the party
because they invited this person who
hurt me.  Last year
is the first shot on the first and
we had a trigger for a
negative emotion is the presence of the thing you do
n't like with the presence of the woman
who has been brought who is already married
in the presence of the object is the 1st
shot art what is the antidote
is the last food is an antidote
must be a lower school
try to avoid all women
tried to avoid all people I'm going to
meet you on a plane
this is a lower school of
dealing with your negative emotions avoid
the project and it's a big part of the
binary of the centers
concentric circles if you never leave the
monastery you're never going to see a woman
then you're never going to have decent so it is then
what ice for who are you going to
meet this week the island doesn't
like to laugh when you hear that says no
the woman come here to bring milk in the
morning from the village cows
and they meet a monk and if a
woman enters the monastery it's
definitely what I'm going to talk to
you about again but you're going to be by your
side with them on a plane next
week if it happens to me
all day hunting these  People,
you have your very big plans, and I was a
little irritated because I said I was going to
stay for an hour, and I had to stay for six
hours. They made these
promises to me, and then they divorced after
a year. I'm sitting here, and the person, the
woman, sits next to me, and she was
crying. And I
think I'm going to charge people ten thousand
dollars if they divorce
after they get married because I only
do it for free. So what I
mean is, the approach is very much about your
negative emotions, about
trying to avoid
what triggers them. We had negative emotions; it's not a very
good system because of
any similar format after
Windows, and when you see the person you
hate, and suddenly your mind is
disenchanted, you have something that isn't
pleasant.
What is the result? We talked a
lot about this in Taiwan. We did Level
10, which is called "Never Get Angry,"
or how not to get angry. I even
decided to call it "Impossible Anger."
And that means that in the kitchen, if
your husband provided you with food, if you understand
the activity, it's impossible for him to have that. It's not that you have to
control it; you can't get
angry,
and this is the
ultimate solution.  The
person who comes from you, I tell you, not
being very active, is a way of
affectionately comforting people who
are irritated by everyone in the group. It
tells them if life is a mirror.
Suddenly they are very quiet and all they
see is the percentage of
irritating people. What you see is a
direct result of the percentage of irritation
within you, how irritating you are towards
other people. And you say that 99
percent of the people in Waziristan are irritating,
so what you're saying is that I
am 100,99% irritating.
So a very trained list keeps quiet
and you can hate other people, but don't
tell them, don't tell anyone because you
are only declaring how irritating you are.
Because what you see is exactly the
percentage.
If you are 25% someone angry, woking, and you
enter a room with four people,
one of them is going to be angry.
That is the highest zone of the path. 9
Father, the truth of the state pointed to a
very large group of great ones, it is from
the most reincarnated of service
farmers, this mixed group, so it has to
adjust its messages and it has to
mix  The lowest school
[Music]
so when we talked about 1610
we went into great detail about a
Santi DeBakey topic before it covers it very well.
Anger has a special ability
that it aims at your bank account of good
seeds. The bank has a unique
ability that should burn your account of
good seeds more than any other
of the 26 million negative ones. Anger
has this ability and it aims at
all your good seeds.
And then when you do the four
powers,
part of the goal is to put the seeds
into sheets of suspended animation,
pause, meaning freeze them. You destroy them,
and that's what you say, okay, you freeze them,
so they never open.
And the same with the mothers with the
positive seeds, it affects them. You can
think about that hardening formation to
have them, but you still have them, but they never
open, which is... wait, it's orange, min,
what's so wrong? The question you're
asking is big. It's
a big topic in the mica grid, like
schemes. In other special conditions,
there's a big discussion.
The karmic object you're talking about is
bodhisattvas. We're talking about bees.
You're talking about normal people, which is...
What burns your bad seeds
if you want to study that, yes, stay
around, they'll probably come to fast,
willows, 15,000, I felt a check, it means
the big problem
about anger and I'll be ready, it's that it
removes your good seeds, it does
n't burn you anymore from yesterday
and I could take the seeds out of the
refrigerator, I say if you can,
but there are books about this subject, it's
a very long story
and then it has sound in your book, it
should be a forest fire or
something like that,
number 4, number 4,
then when you take measures in the afternoon, in
the afternoons this week,
you can just follow these pictures, it's very
effective,
Peter, just follow the pictures this
afternoon if you have time after yours and it's
throwing fort, meditate in the
burning forest, Ouija, waiting for your husband
with the flu, my life, my philosophy,
Télam, you're a fool
and I didn't do what you think I
did and you're a fool, etc., etc.,
but
good karma, angry with me, I'm
angry with you, that I don't hate you so much,
but I'm just going to ignore you, I'm not even
going to get angry, you don't
deserve to be the person that I
tell you about Gallego,
the  The best way to show
your anger at this peak is to stay calm. They want to
make you angry; they have to see you angry.
Just smile at them, belittle them. It's like, "I'm
angry with you, but I don't
want any seeds
because you're worthless."
And there's a joke in Buddhism that if you
really want to irritate your enemy, be
successful and happy. What we did
was the most irritating thing. The enemy doesn't fight
with them; they
just have fun. Knowing how to take care of things and have a
good life is the best way to irritate
them. I specialize in that. We'll be
back with a little more. If we're
going to take a break,
White taught them this morning that those are
some ways to keep your students
in your class, even if you're not going to stop anytime
soon. But I am.
When people kill each other, when they
hit each other, when they
attack each other, or online, it's all
because of number two, and it's all due to the
negative emotion number two, which is anger.
All this war,
these cities.
I lived where I live now, in the desert, or I
live in the smallest legal house you
can have. I
spend a lot of time planting trees.
I want trees, and it's very difficult. It's like...
Like teaching them how to teach their
cousin, people take a lot of patience, it takes
many years to give them water, taking care of them. I
go to the television, to the internet, and see that
someone is bombing another country.
But it didn't take long for
that tree to grow. Do you know how much work
people do to destroy themselves, to grow that
tree, and you just destroy it with a
bomb? It's
extremely destructive and it destroys
the hymen. And many, many years of work
to build cities, competitions, to
plant trees,
have children and take care of them, and then kill them.
It's tremendously recitative, and it's just a
thought, it's just a movement of the
mind, feeling. They are just
thoughts that describe
countries that outrage, that kill millions of
people.
Every person who dies, their mother
worked hard for them, like drug traffickers,
they worked so hard to give them so that
this child was born, to feed them. The father
worked for the money, and then you just
send them to fight in a stupid war
that means nothing.
I gave a talk at a
military academy in America, and there are all these young people, young
20-year-olds who are going to be
the tough pilots, and then they go back
home without legs. It's not
romantic anymore, don't believe
any stations.  linked
efe jmr
rambo movie very famous in china
stop stealing horrible things from
America don't you see things don't take don't steal
these violent things these
violent movies steal from us with tap with it's not
romantic the person to live from their
houses their legs arrive at their house without
legs their whole life is destroyed they are
alcoholics
war is not romantic
shooting people in the movie is not
noble and camps it all comes from
2 seconds of a mental movement
all the war all the death from an
idea and it's that he fights and wants to be a
hero or a military hero destroys fight
with this don't destroy trees there are children
[Music]
[Applause]
if you can't control your anger and boat
strike
will destroy countries and thousands of people we
love you so ok
add two more lines of I promise well
it's good power of numbers formulas for
number two if it's not for number one and
some but number 2 here
they think who x killed her
then there was a custom in the
monasteries of Tibet
a lama who gets very angry interest in me
because in Buddhism you should
n't say  Nothing bad about Tula,
especially Atlantic. Then there was
a secondary language,
this chip.
If you're the one who shares the trustee of
a pop, there was a tradition of calling her "
never wastes money," but it means
the program is never going to give a payment.
But you shouldn't say it. Those people
made this language. It's a language
to refer to Tula. It makes you, the
mark, your faults, the program, in a
polite way.
For example, here people call me "the
heart of my saint, she loves it, sometimes she gets
hot." It means that she hits two
boys, her students. So they say, "It's
the heart of my saint, she loves it,
sometimes she gets hot," and it means that she gets angry. So
she gets angry and hits us, not very often,
but the heart, the mass, gets
hot sometimes. Maybe talking about that,
Pavón Casting was a very honest person,
and he said things that other people were
n't going to say. He
would see those, the tallest, the most
reincarnated, and what he saw, he looked them in the eyes
and said, "Even if I look, don't get angry, don't get angry
with your students. I'm not going to
say that you're hot in your heart. I'm going to
tell you the truth. You're a very
bad example. You're a..."  reincarnated unlam has
reincarnated but you're a bad example and
he said it and then gmt many
problems but oh well and whoever wants to
but if you can
give them a name of beni in of
polite nickname chat when he protected him state
between you in the park
it is said they give they give tablet taboo
ruling of eating soup soup table travel
cat a fact that I got in charge of
then
wiggins suns gray tapas in Sanskrit
these layers tapes
hits peace became like an enemy
at the spiritual hour what does a
practical death of a full
like Rambo mean a tough guy rough practices
who is a tough guy
who is a strong guy they love him will be one
of my lamas who stopped a train
tried to move and didn't move and the
train didn't move
he is a strong guy tough guy these are the ones
who separate sun all day in the snow
meditates in the snow the days something like that they
say wow he
is a spiritual warrior and everything
stopped the train wow
the merit for two days in the snow and not
opening his eyes this is a la mar carries
says true this is not a guy  Rude, okay, okay,
gentle, so what is a
strong type? This woman who can't go where you
think I'm going to [ __ ]? A strong type is a
woman who is full of work and her
husband yells at her and she stays calm. She's
a warrior. That's a
spiritual warrior. Don't tell me about the people who
sit in the snow. Don't tell me anything
about the woman who stopped a train.
That's not difficult
compared to staying calm when
someone is yelling at you. It's much
harder than stopping a train or sitting
in the snow for two days
with Cesc, calm in the kitchen when
your husband is going crazy. Is it a
spiritual situation? It's those women in
the kitchen who use emptiness, who take
refuge in Baku, in emptiness, and don't yell
back. That's a warrior. Two
pivots. Those people deserve this
war medal that they give in America. In
China there's probably one, but those are
the people who are
different. That's what they deserve. Not these
people who shoot with a gun. Do
you have one or not? That doesn't deserve
recognition. Courage comes from those who do
n't yell in the kitchen. That's truly
beautiful.
Is a woman a spiritual warrior?  He doesn't shout
because he wants to stop people from shouting.
I want to stop the war. The people who
stop wars are braver than
those who fight wars. Gay people, and the
people who stop wars in their
own minds are braver than those
who have wars on the
ground. That's more. He needs more courage.
He's a war hero on the front
line. It says,
if you evaluate
bad karma, Nambu Ward, in evaluating it,
anger
is the worst because it destroys
all good families. It doesn't mean there isn't
anger. It's the current
prince,
the worst main emotion.
Second is patience on the list of
war heroes. People who
know how to stay calm, who can keep their
patience, it's much harder than
shooting people or dropping bombs. That's not
so difficult, you just stop the trigger
to stay calm in the kitchen.
If your husband has been there for a month, an hour, a
week, a month,
then those are warriors. If you can
do that, then you should be
proud. If you can stay calm in
the kitchen while people are yelling at you,
technological, and you say, "Oh,
come on, the rhythm, I'm not going to be
hungry, this, I'm not going to stay
calm."  I'm
not going to answer what he invented. Less
rest than before, be warriors. We
only have half an hour and we're going to
think about what would be fun to do
because everything we talked about was very depressing.
Jordi, yes, we have another job this
week that I mentioned before. Today
we're doing a review of all the
past years
that you can do in the afternoon if you want
and it doesn't have so much...  Or work
especially you would like to be
in the training it says there that it didn't
have meditation up if you want to be
in crisis if you want to specialize in
wire or meditate and development
then reason to live here we're going to have to do
more but I talk a lot that
[Music]
leftovers from Thailand I'm sorry
we're so busy in
Thailand I'm
in the one where a woman is working on
a computer
dears
and we're giving a review of all
the hunger in images the
socialization exam and we
show you the image and you tell me the
story the story without the one it says and
you tell me what it means that I'm going to be
checking from tomorrow I'm
going to show you images and you
tell me what it's about
so try to memorize the image and
what it means ok
this list of time
I'll talk more and maybe square and the
images are square personal and they
also have colors in them
Tim is going to print them maybe today
venerable has something fun that maybe
you want to
try to find the number of
steps in the translation that connects to the
parable the image so I'm
working with the Tibetan but if you
want  Have fun like the translators
from China, and this image is on this
page
of the book.
In the beginning,
the first job is to sell
the courses. When you start teaching the
courses, you have to tell them how cool
a Buddhist tradition is going to be. In
Buddhism, selling the teachings before
giving them is like when you sell lessons,
exactly like selling.
So here comes the couple, you
grab them and tell them how great
the stereo in this car is. There's no
stereo like this, no car in the
whole world, and these tires are
round.
You have to talk about things according to
tradition. We're at this part, we have
n't reached rhyme
78 yet.
You're starting the hunger because we've just
started the hunger, and because
we're at image 78. Because I started
this course backwards,
I taught the end of the rhyme first. Why would I do
that?
Because it's the meditation part.
Yes, my strategies for eight years
were to start at the end of the book, and
we studied variety, and we studied
meditation called Vipassana.
The path ended
with visiting, and we studied the book, the
end of the book first, because we wanted to
use the seeds within the
niece. It's that we had to talk about
emptiness.  And then he wants to promote
meditation, and what do we want to do now?
We're going to jump to another topic, Islam, which I won't
cover again. At the end of this book,
I'm going to cover the same topics, but from him.
All the images
related to meditation are already finished, and he was talking about taking
care of yourself. It's not very long here,
and because he didn't want to compete with
the guys who had already done it better,
then the link is there. I was at
one of the points to sell the hunger
work. Look,
you can do it. It's
big, it takes years, and you can do it
high, and that's all.
Don't resist.
Nice picture of you, you're going to repeat it
when you take the exam. And after
these weeks that are coming, he's learning
on this screen, in this image. The dad
is learning
because of the signs the daughter has. She has to
teach the dad to be
forward because he's from the
paper generation, as you can see, Michael, and it's very
difficult for us. And people tell me, "
Dr. Gul's wife again, I'm just
going to send you a Twitter widget."
She took my phone, a
phone widget, and tapped the
black button to send an email, and he told me to tap it
here. That's why I have it.
around because he teaches me how to use these
things, he's not afraid of them, he
has this beautiful quality
of not being afraid of new
technology, only the handling tests,
the company calls him and they say not
all of them lose
and he says nothing, excuse me, he has
courage
and I tend to get scared with them, I don't
want to learn it,
I think if it were three years it will already
be obsolete and you don't have to learn it, I'm not, I don't
know, anyway
that attitude, I
'm not, what do I know, I'm not, I'm not a nun, I ca
n't, I have a
job, I'm busy, I can't learn
any thousand-page text and meditate on
it,
recently, what this image, if it is, that I'm like
the father,
the father, I don't understand this Facebook thing, it's
explaining without equal, which is something
new,
the options that can withstand, I do
n't have, you have, because my job, I can't
become a music teacher, what
can you tell me, of course I'm going to
do it in the video,
dv
integra, I've explained space, I'm going to
explain once and then you're going to have to
do it three times, get old, you have to
be an Englishman,
be successful, and the point of this image
is that you  You can do it
next time. All your life, what made
your whole life
difficult, says in his book, my son. This
is very easy.
This is very easy for me to talk about. We ca
n't understand my sentences.
Really, they are the invisible points.
And if you don't make a habit of the difficult things in your
life, you're going to go back to that group because of the
difficult things. If there's a problem with
your partner or something, you don't want to talk about
it
because of the difficult points because it's easy. It's that they are
easy.
If you see this image, what are you going to tell me?
Fear? Don't be afraid of this new
technology called Lambert, and
learn new things.
Most people stop
learning after the time you
can see college, and they get out of the
habit of learning new things. And those
rare people who keep learning
all their lives, like code, are very, very
good minds. It's that their minds
become more and more cultured. I'm not afraid
of the seventh spurt. Don't say it's too
long, that you can't do anything about it, and it's
in the Disney things from ITJuve. The
next image is
why you shouldn't go to
teacher training. It sits on a
hill in a classroom. I was saying that it's a
list of low motivations for coming to
teaching.
So it's an image of this ship,
number one, it's a camping plan. It's bad to
come to the teaching because you want it. It's
a blessing to be there. No, it's not
bad. It's bad if that's the only thing you
want. It's about people who
say, "I'm not going to do anything about it." Now that I'm in
the petticoat, but I won't understand it,
but it's a blessing to be there. Okay, that's
fine, but it's stupid.
Some of
these big things
before entering the room, I can't
understand it,
and that's why you're coming. So,
word for word, special, it says
that because your friends,
the water, the farm, because all
my friends are going, because my friends, and
that's what the image means.
Now you know what this
image means. When you see it, you're going to say, "I
'm talking about the five reasons
for it,
but only one
[Music]
because my friends are going, three
to get more information, so I
can teach something for myself, trying to
improve. I don't just want to know here, the
lowest middle school to teach, okay?
Motivation is a teaching without
applying it, just like you never take
a teaching without applying it to yourself.
Besides, Washington, on this,
despising your motorcycle  And although the excuse does
n't collect if it doesn't collect
knowledge of excuses, I teach you,
learn, still follow the capital letters in
you, in you, and we add it
to the school only in a very
good way, we had a very, very good
explanation from the teacher, then
power for power, and it means I'm going to
have a higher position with the
teachers, I did more things,
people were impressed with me,
although I'm going to have more power over the
people who ask you, I'm going to be the
teacher and not the number one student, it's like
impressing, and if we say speech
that these Fujimorist groups, that
someone says, how do I
recommend it,
nothing, and you tell them, they're not
seeing, I do have the school, just half,
let me in,
and look, like in number 8, you want to
help, you want to impress him, of all you
know, that to impress the
head at the party, you're not, there are
five reasons why you shouldn't
go to one, on top of that, it's law, and
mainly it's the opposite of
Clay's intention to apply it when applying the
teaching to one's own life, and that should
be me or fun, your only motivation,
if I'm sick I'm going to take my
treatment in Diamond and Spike,
Buddhism is  called mmmm betis
to desmanes m
already the whole retreat is medical treatment
where is it going to be next week I'm
going to America that has de monte for
mental treatment
this disease called anger desire in
arc and I'm going because they treat me very
well
castro-wright is the right motivation
boss teacher fabio yes she treated me very well
and if I take the treatment I'll be able to
give it to other people
that's the right motivation jacques
turn the next
hector already the air
is about explaining the theory of
relativity you don't recognize it and it's on the
plane says let's see
from when he says no you start explaining
quantum physics to him
someone starts explaining atomic physics and I
tell everyone that everything is wrong sometimes sometimes
people start
explaining to me the diamond extinguisher that
happened recently and I'm just polite and I
tell them that I don't say that I don't say that
25 years ago
in that I just say if you put the point
here you are there you would be as I said yesterday in
the hunger
comes from a lioness who knows in English and
in language we have this in English we have
this language that says  Or he's a know-
it-all, violin-shaped, but the Buddha
really is the know-it-all. If he broadcasts, he
sees everything in all times,
including what you think, what you follow for the
over before an Aris, and your internal thoughts,
and the same is the same,
wow. So he wrote
the sutras for you personally,
even though a tablet, don't doubt it, a book he
wrote
in April 2019. He has
this ability. You don't
have that ability,
so you're wasting your time. And
the reason I'm here is to make you
Buddha, that's me, so you
can write teachings for people
who come two thousand years later. Okay, you don't
understand?
Here, you're not talking about a doctor,
the future of your baby, the future of your
illness, and you need
radiation treatment because it's going to
cure you in six months, three days, and
all hours. When they give you a teaching, it's
only for you, and it's exactly what
you mean. What does it mean to waste
time with other kinds of teachings?
Personally, it seems crazy to me. To me, it's
possible to get a
teaching from a person who has a
mind from 2500 years ago and knows everything about
your life and  Knowing your future, you know you're coming
back and they're already
communicating. I used to sit when I had
the Buddha, future of gays, Michael is
having a bad day,
don't worry. In my time,
who do you talk to when you're in the bathroom? Do
n't worry anymore,
get a teaching from someone like that,
then you don't have to add anything to it, don't
worry. It drives me
crazy when people say this
Buddhism just needs a little more
psychology of names and psychology number
54.
The books are going to disappear
and that's what's happening at the airport this
weekend. I tell myself that in ambition,
knowing 10, Vicente knows what they're
talking about and life and tong and sadism
need this book of
rearming site. Well, it irritates me more now
and I'm going to teach this language whether they like it or
not, it
allows them to say it. How it drives me
crazy, like a charger fix, people try to
fix
or add challenges to something.
The Diamond Cutter is the most
viewed book in history,
I have more copies than the Bible. Okay, it's
probably fine, probably I do
n't need it,
and well, look, I wouldn't have survived if I
wasn't useful.
A Diamond Cutter wouldn't have
helped anyone, I'd be out there
trying to  deceive but feel and with all
waste your time we need to learn
something that wasn't written by someone of
mine feels like something to write to
someone from psychology that last year
and the colors that have 30 have 40 or
but you have to say also a time
to read all the crap that is
available with time and all that
is time to watch hanging on YouTube
when this cat jumping with what
scares
well because I have sent this video
about so much I don't have taxes and
dying
Tizimín and I have so much I only know I already know
how many miners I don't have time says
for this book of cinema vigil and everyone old
age helps me makes me appreciate
more than I tell you this don't waste your
time on the big and don't resist
technology jumping jumps
is very difficult this middle ground is
very difficult I don't care so much about it
and therefore Instagram acquires I
am 66 years old telling you that
your storms are solvent don't
waste a minute of your life on that you do
n't have time if you work very hard
maybe it is wasted in this time
on these cats
definitely not it  You go and you don't have, we can't
watch movies,
that's Buddhist, learn to relax,
go see how we were on DirecTV, the
next day we were better students
because we had relaxed, you can't
watch so many states
if you're so tired that you can't do
anything else, if you need a break
I recommend
but don't waste, study watching it, rest,
rest, but you will be the best
Buddhist and rest while you watch the movies, we went
with his mom and then we started
washing all the contrasts and it was very
difficult, don't tell me, after two days
we were then sometimes
the many bad seeds is that it's a
skill,
how to go see a movie, Edwin
Martinez,
sometimes we go to do nothing and we really
eat
in scene
anyone,
already everyone at once,
the second time,
but don't waste your time and
firmware, if you can work, work, if you can't, you can't
work,
I'm not against cats,
I'm just saying don't do it all the
time, it's okay, we finished fighting, we finished, it's over, time is over,
we're going to start with the other one
tomorrow, I
was sending it very well, we're going to make
a mountain, first Luca
is the CSU, yes, but it's like that,
what is
good
next to me,
no, no,
yes  Not
here
[Music]
Hello
to me
[Music] Yes,
actually, no,
thank you for coming, thank you for working
so hard, and we want to welcome you this
morning and we'll probably give you the
readings with the codes, and I said this is
the review of the last few years of
Hunger and Casey Warner in case you
want to major in that